so next up for your viewing pleasure is a video where a woman named lizzie accuses me of being
anti-semitic for being against israeli government and the genocide of palestinians and uh for you
know politicians being quiet about this because they don't want to upset donors and they don't
want to upset corporate money etc etc um but she's gonna attempt to do a lot of that's my move for
to make her argument righteous when it is not um i don't stand alone in being against the israeli
government uh i stand with many and the attempts to defame people like myself are not made in love
they are not made in regard to humanity no they are made in the effort of being able to continue to
move forward with the genocide of the people without the world holding anyone accountable for it you're
literally using your time to defame individuals who are standing against war crimes you're attempting
to defame me in support of that is a defamation of yourself the truth though is that this is not okay
this is bullying and harassment as it is actually laid out in the bylaws of these social media apps
she should not be allowed to try to diminish my livelihood undermine my personhood challenge my
character because i am against the genocide of palestinians and the factors at work that are
allowing it to happen this is the actual energy that should be flagged because when people like this
get away with this they silence people from protecting the people who are already voiceless
and that cannot stand any longer the genocide of palestine because so many people feel so confident
to comment who are simply just not informed i'm informed af like every day like the first thing
i do when i wake up at 6 30 a.m is like engorge myself with what i missed while i was sleeping
this is amanda seals she's a comedian she has over 2 million followers on instagram but she's decided
to devote all of her recent content to demonizing israel she's a self-proclaimed expert on the subject of
israel and palestine and she is informed af i'm sure she has a wonderful grasp on the thousands of
years of history amanda has even called those who are asking for the release of the hostages
genocide supporters amanda's videos have been filled with anti-semitic propaganda lies and
misinformation let's take a look at one of them from yesterday real question real question real
question what the are these elected officials that we put in office doing
what are y'all doing it's really just about money amanda do you know how offensive and ignorant it
is to say that american elected officials are only standing with israel because it's really just about
money regardless of whatever you're trying to imply with these ancient anti-semitic tropes about
jewish wealth and influence the reality is that these american elected officials stand with the
democratic frontline ally israel because we share common interests and values and we also share a
common enemy so the reason that the u.s and other allied democratic governments aren't protecting
hamas is because on october 7th they showed us that they are worse than isis on a single day
hamas terrorists murdered over 1400 innocent civilians torturing 80 of them and raping women so brutally
that they shattered their bones at least 240 including american civilians are currently being held hostage
by hamas in the gaza strip oh and amanda back to your earlier point about genocide hamas has a
genocidal charter that calls for the murder of all jews this threatens america as much as israel
if anything we should be thanking our elected officials especially our members of congress for their
continued support of israel and i strongly urge them to approve military defense aid support for israel
as soon as possible